[
  {
    "id": "4e69ed27-ff44-4a47-a1d8-e67284fccff5",
    "front": "duis",
    "back": "pede posuere nonummy",
    "topic_id": "18048ee6-4b4b-45bc-9cb5-fd502749f3b9"
  },
  {
    "id": "7c96ee89-9723-42f1-94d7-e8deb5a39d9f",
    "front": "et magnis dis",
    "back": "in leo",
    "topic_id": "18048ee6-4b4b-45bc-9cb5-fd502749f3b9"
  },
  {
    "id": "835c8961-50f1-465c-a010-b4e040619899",
    "front": "vulputate luctus",
    "back": "ut odio cras",
    "topic_id": "18048ee6-4b4b-45bc-9cb5-fd502749f3b9"
  },
  {
    "id": "58f94167-90ed-4ed5-9b11-2e5b121096c7",
    "front": "rhoncus mauris enim",
    "back": "ac lobortis vel",
    "topic_id": "18048ee6-4b4b-45bc-9cb5-fd502749f3b9"
  },
  {
    "id": "8249b1fc-49a6-4710-9160-57bc27e75d58",
    "front": "tempor turpis nec",
    "back": "cras mi",
    "topic_id": "18048ee6-4b4b-45bc-9cb5-fd502749f3b9"
  },
  {
    "id": "eaf97874-cebd-4b2f-b6ab-15257c2311b7",
    "front": "erat curabitur gravida",
    "back": "etiam pretium iaculis",
    "topic_id": "18048ee6-4b4b-45bc-9cb5-fd502749f3b9"
  },
  {
    "id": "ccc76884-7e51-45e3-8f79-f29c40297de2",
    "front": "fusce",
    "back": "justo in",
    "topic_id": "18048ee6-4b4b-45bc-9cb5-fd502749f3b9"
  },
  {
    "id": "7ecea763-ba73-4f70-b5ef-221e082cff3e",
    "front": "congue risus",
    "back": "in felis donec",
    "topic_id": "18048ee6-4b4b-45bc-9cb5-fd502749f3b9"
  },
  {
    "id": "25719f2d-89f0-4ac6-a8cd-61814c437c7b",
    "front": "natoque penatibus",
    "back": "vel",
    "topic_id": "18048ee6-4b4b-45bc-9cb5-fd502749f3b9"
  },
  {
    "id": "10f7ed5c-8ab0-49ee-b9a4-72408dd81ac4",
    "front": "nulla",
    "back": "duis bibendum felis",
    "topic_id": "18048ee6-4b4b-45bc-9cb5-fd502749f3b9"
  }
]